Started this timeline On the exact same day
We've been reading the map In the exact same way
When the room gets loud And the colors start to
blur I pull up a chair I'm your anchor, I'm sure
Wherever you are, I am holding the line Your
schedule is written right next to mine
To be a giant, to stare like a wall I know all the
angles to keep you from the fall Using the
leverage, perfectly aligned Leaving the noise
of the outside be heard I am your player 2 Plugged
into the board We're facing the static with a
single core Through the absolute chaos
Whatever we do I am sitting right here I am player
2 Yeah I am player 2
I don't have a heavy crane to lift up the sky But I
know how to pivot when the danger is high A quiet
technician when the system runs cold A shield in
the center When the story unfolds You send me the
signal A tap on the hand I'm the closest defense
That you have in this land
I don't need to be a giant to stand like a wall I
know all the angles to keep you from the fall
Using the leverage, perfectly aligned Leaving
the noise of the outside behind I am your player 2
Plugged into the board We're facing the static
with a single chord Through the absolute chaos
Whatever we do I am sitting right here I am player
I am player 2
When the variables crash and the world walks
away I am locking the perimeter I'm gonna stay
You're the heart of this house You're the center
of the spinning I'll never let the cold of the
outside in
I am your
player two, plugged into the void We're facing
the static with a single chord Through the
absolute chaos, whatever we do I am sitting
right here I am player two Right by your side From
the very first day Play it slow It's locked in Ooh
Ooh